<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-09-10T14:23:56+02:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Fjellkjede</title><subtitle>Decentralized systems and blockchain utility apps made easy.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Manage your miners from home</title><link href="/blog/remote-management/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Manage your miners from home" /><published>2018-10-07T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/blog/remote-management</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/remote-management/">&lt;p&gt;The times when you could have a few miners running at home is history. Let Fjellkjede worry about the electricity, network, cooling and operations of your miners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, the challenge for small- and medium sized miners are to find an affordable and reliable place to place the miners. This is where Fjellkjede comes in. We make sure your miners are up, and so that you can keep an eye on them with VPN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our VPN offering include both software and hardware measures to keep communication secure.  Key components in this easy to use VPN offering is &lt;a href=&quot;https://zerotier.com&quot;&gt;Zerotier&lt;/a&gt; and an OrangePi.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Let us make sure your miners are up, and you'll do the management</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/r2.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Data center in Norway?</title><link href="/blog/data-center-norway/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Data center in Norway?" /><published>2018-10-07T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/blog/data-center-norway</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/data-center-norway/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;prime-location-for-data-centers&quot;&gt;Prime location for data centers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cushmanwakefield.co.uk/en-gb/research-and-insight/2016/data-centre-risk-index-2016&quot;&gt;Cushman &amp;amp; Wakefield DATA CENTRE RISK INDEX 2016&lt;/a&gt;, ranked Norway number 2, just after Iceland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to do business in Norway, and the political climate is stable. For mining operations, more important is the cost of electricity and climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electricity in Norway is affordable, but more importantly it’s 100% green, clean and hydroelectric. By placing your miners at Fjellkjede’s facilities, you don’t have to think about any environmental impact. It’s all clean. In Fjellkjede’s customized facilities, we’ve built them with energy efficiency in mind where we exploit the cool climate in Norway. For example, we use very little energy for cooling compared to old fashioned data centres.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Norway is ranked #2 for best location for data centers globally.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/Data_Centre_Risk_Index_Report_2016_web_pdf.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Custom ASIC hosting</title><link href="/blog/custom-offering/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Custom ASIC hosting" /><published>2018-10-07T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/blog/custom-offering</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/custom-offering/">&lt;p&gt;We let others take the multi-megawatt orders. Because we focus on the small to medium sized orders, we are also able to customize. If you have special needs or requests for your miners, we are happy to discuss and find good solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can customize any part of the service, from shipping and delivery to management and operations. We can even help you with purchasing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Small orders, means custom delivery</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/images/r1.jpg" /></entry></feed>
